lifeisastudent.com 2010-04-17

# LifeisaStudent - Privacy Policy

privacy policy

LifeisaStudent.com is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK.

**1.** When you register, you provide us with your name, address, email address and what university or school you go to. This allows us to process and create your profile. You have the option to withhold personal information that is not required for profile creation process.

**2.** We use your personal information to update you about new products/services.

**3.** We will only contact you with our newsletter or other details about student life, if you wish to unsubscribe to this at anytime you may.

**4.** We may share your personal information preferences and statistics with any third party for commercial reasons, such as which university you attend, or how many videos you have uploaded/watched and may use that for our purposes but never actually disclose your personal information.

**5.** In order to process any credit/debit card transactions, the bank or card processing agency may require verifying your personal details for authorisation outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Your information will not be transferred outside the EEA for any other purpose.

**6.** We use a technology called "cookies" as part of a normal business procedure to track patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. A cookie is an element of data that our Website sends to your browser which is then stored on your system. You can set your browser to prevent this happening. Any information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you change your browser settings.

**7.** We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details at any time.

**8.** We will not transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) without first obtaining your consent.

**9.** We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.

If you have any questions about privacy please contact us at:

LifeisaStudent.com  
7 Darwin Court  
Lichfield  
WS13 8FN

Tel: 08458 333 444

Email: [help@lifeisastudent.com](mailto:%20contact@lifeisastudent.com)
